dailybruin.com 2017-12-14

# Privacy policy | Daily Bruin

### Visitors

Like most website operators, the Daily Bruin collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. The Daily Bruin’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how the Daily Bruin’s visitors use its website. The Daily Bruin also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. The Daily Bruin does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to the Daily Bruin’s websites choose to interact with the Daily Bruin in ways that require the Daily Bruin to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that the Daily Bruin gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who comment to an email address. In each case, the Daily Bruin collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with the Daily Bruin. The Daily Bruin does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

the Daily Bruin may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, the Daily Bruin may monitor the most popular articles or comments on the dailybruin.com site. The Daily Bruin may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, the Daily Bruin does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

the Daily Bruin discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on the Daily Bruin’s behalf or to provide services available at the Daily Bruin’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Daily Bruin’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. The Daily Bruin will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, the Daily Bruin discloses potentially personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when the Daily Bruin believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of the Daily Bruin, third parties or the public at large. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. The Daily Bruin takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. The Daily Bruin uses cookies to help the Daily Bruin identify and track visitors, and their website access preferences. The Daily Bruin visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Daily Bruin’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of the Daily Bruin’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by the Daily Bruin and does not cover the use of cookies or tracking pixels by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, the Daily Bruin may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in its sole discretion. The Daily Bruin encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

### Legal Actions & Disputes

By accessing this website, user agrees that jurisdiction and venue for any and all legal actions or disputes against the Daily Bruin and any of its employees shall be governed by the laws of the United States of America and the State of California.
